webzlinks.com 2016-10-31

# Privacy Policy -

We want you to feel confident that the information we collect, and that you choose to share, will be treated with care.

This PP does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people we do not employ or manage. Our website contain hyperlinks to third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites or advertisers. Please check with those websites to determine their privacy policy.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect your personal information when you register with us, when you use our products or services, or when you visit our web pages or the pages of certain of our partners. We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

During a normal visit to our websites, no personal information about you is collected. All information is free to browse at your leisure without the need for you to provide us with any personal information. Your visit does however generate a session log. When you visit any website, the server housing the pages automatically generates a "session log." The logs are used by the owners of the sites to track the pages you visit or request. The only data gathered is the Internet Protocol (IP) address from which you came (which contains no personal information), the website that referred you, the pages you visited and the date and time of those visits. We use session logs to help us determine how people travel through our site. In this way, we can structure our pages so that the information most frequently visited is easier to find. By tracking page visits, we can also determine if the information we're providing is being used. 

When you register for the download of our products or services, we may ask for information such as your name, date of birth, gender, email address, and general location. We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request. Log data is only used in aggregate to analyze usage of our website.

We use your personal information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

We will not contact minor children about special offers or for marketing purposes.

We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested or when we have your permission.

We display targeted advertisements based on your personal information. We do not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. Our advertisers may assume that if you interact with, view, or click on targeted ads, then you meet the targeting criteria. We may work with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in industries and categories of business different from ours.

We reserve the right to publish non-personally identifiable, summary information regarding visitors to our websites for promotional purposes and as a representative audience for advertisers. This is not your personal information, only general summaries of the activities of our visitors and customers.
